Sick
Ache
My head's... killing me!
Sick
Where are my
phone and wallet?
What is this, Hell on Earth?
Thanks for everything, Mom.
It's the
apocalypse.
I can't move
an inch...
Soul
I've never had a hangover this bad before!
There's bad energy
in the air.
Grew up watching
Glitter Force
I don't remember anything after
the fifth bamboo shooty.
Don't try to bluff your way out of this.
Why do I get the feeling
Mizuhara was over at my place?
What's with these fragmented happy memories?
Sick
Ache
Mizuhara took care... of me?
Would she ever
do that!?
I must've been dreaming.
Hmm?
A group invite?
Team Gold Ship
Sasano invited you to join.
Oh, from last night.
Wow, they're talking a bunch.
That was so much fun!
Sasano
Wanna drink again-no-jutsu.
Kawanaka
I see a ninja!
I'm so hungover
Pant
Hold up! Last night's group?
Does that mean...
Pant
Ichinose Chizuru
Mizuhara's...
meow
private contact?!
Mizuhara Memo
I had so much fun today!
See you soon. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
What are you wearing today?
*pant*
Let me explain!
The "Mizuhara Chizuru"
contact info he already had
is a rental girlfriend account
that Diamond created.
That means the agency checks it, too,
and if he tried to send her private
messages without any bookings,
it'd be considered a breach
of the terms of service.
A bunch of scary people would visit him,
and he'd be in all sorts of trouble.
You guys be careful on social media, too!
Ichinose Chizuru
I'm in!
I'm in, somehow!
What is that? A cat?
Why does it look so cute to me?
Ba-dump
Forgot all about the hangover
Is that Mizuhara's shadow? Cute!
W
o
h
Every guy has gone through this at least once
Wait, can I really look at this?
Add friend
Could I take this chance
to add her as a friend?
No, hang on.
Wouldn't she get a request?
Uh, wha? Die.
Decline
BEEP
Gah! Anything but that!
Besides, I may have caused her
all kinds of trouble last night.
I can't be aggressive here.
Add friend
Tremble
plonk
I can't do it.
"Friend"? It's way too scary.
Ugh. All that squirming made
my head hurt even more.
Sway    Sway
A mandatory class? Now?
Are you trying to kill me?
Boo!
Boo
Yo, Green Man.
He looks more blue than green to me.
You look like a ghost.
R... Rawr.
Gloom
It's last night's group.
Your hangover all right?
Far from it.
Duh, after how much you drank.
Where's Mizuhara? Is she here?
Oh, yeah, where's Chizuru-chan?
Flinch
She gets so
hung up over
that stuff.
She's running solo today.
She's still mad at me for
inviting boys to the pub.
She's... mad?
Well, yeah.
flinch
Her secret may have stayed hidden,
but that was an awful boozer.
You guys gonna be okay? Sorry about that.
She's mad... She's mad, huh?
Don't worry about it. She's always like that.
So it really was a dream?
I made her mad and then had
such a convenient dream...
I'm such a piece of trash.
Seriously.
Sparkle
Ahahaha
Hahaha
For real?
Life is
all about
fish food pellets.
Sick
Ache
I'm so done...
My head hurts so much...
Sick
Ache
It's gotten worse 'cause I pushed myself.
I remember nothing
about the class...
This ain't going away until tomorrow.
Fish food?
No, I can't...!!
If I had a girlfriend right about now,
would she take care of me all nicely?
What are you
fantasizing about?
A-Anyway, I gotta hydrate.
Take a good look
at reality, man.
Drunkard!
It wasn't a dream...
God! Which is it?!
What even is the truth?!
I can't ask Mizuhara!
Why don't I remember anything?!
Kinoshita Kazuya
Add friend
Block
Plonk
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Karaoke Village
"Ex and Girlfriend"
Staaare
Stare...
Why have you been staring at me?
Don't you have something to say to me?
Standing
By
Huh? Something to say?
I figured it was about time
you made up your mind.
My mind? About what?
Ow!
Eek
Don't make me spell it out!
What is it?!
The rest of the convo... from back then.
Bear with me, Ruka-chan!
There's something I need to say.
R-Right...
I mean, surely Chizuru-san
It's here.
My time
has come...!!
won't come between us after we
spent a passionate night together!
So it's only a matter of time before
you decide to go out with me for real!
Oh, that turned out okay.
What?! No way!
Was she still asleep?
Did she not hear it?!
Nah, she just believed me.
What?! She believed you?!
She believed that nothing happened,
even though I spent the night at your place?
Y-Yeah, though she took some convincing.
Lies! There's no way!
You should really tell her the truth!
The truth is that nothing happened!
Crazy
It can't be...
Despite the undeniable fact that I stayed
over, she believed in his innocence?
In Kazuya-kun, of all people?
Those two have clearly gotten closer!
Dazed
Then I know what I must do!
Wait, I'm not done.
Customer is king.
Welcome...
Oh, hello, Kazu-kun!
M... Mami-chan...
Sweat
Why is Mami-chan here?
Just bad luck?
No, that can't be.
Did she hear from someone
that I was working here?
S-Solo karaoke? Do you do this often?
I'm here to finish up my report.
Using this as my study room.
PC
R-Report? I see.
I heard from Kibe-chan
that you got a job here.
And I happened to be in the area,
so I figured I'd stop by and mess with you.
Just kidding!
Kibe! I knew it!
Please don't.
I've actually been here before.
It was with a friend, though.
I know! I know all about it!
But I can't say I watched it all!
Okay, two hours in a Joyfound room.
I might extend.
In that case, we have free time plans, too.
Kazuya-kun, do you know her?
Oh, crap!
Technically
Current
GF
I feel like letting her talk to
Ruka-chan is a really bad idea!
Huh? Y-Yeah, we go to the
same college. Same year.
Wow, what a cutie!
Crap, she took the bait!
Are you in school?
I shouldn't let them talk too much!
Yes, I am.
O-Okay, let me take me to your room.
We're busy and all.
Oh, sure.
Huh? But there's hardly anyone here.
This way, this way.
Coming.
Seriously, good on you for working.
It's no big deal. I'm just part-time, anyway.
Wow, I could never stick with it.
You're trying to grow up,
aren't you, Kazu-kun?
Come on. You're no different.
You're plugging away at college.
Ka...
RUMBLE
Kazu-kun?!
Here you go.
Your glass for unlimited drinks.
Thanks, and sorry about this.
I got part of this done back home,
but I kept getting lazy.
Oh, your report? It's no problem at all.
Thank God they didn't interact much.
Who knows what'd happen if Mami-chan
and Ruka-chan went at it for real?
We went to karaoke together twice, didn't we?
Y-Yeah.
Back then, I was losing my mind at being
alone in a room with her for the first time
Wow, you're way off-key.
A
h
a
and was desperately trying to hide it.
Stare...
Staaare
JOLT
Ruka-chan?!
Busted
Why'd she follow us?
Wait, did she hear all that?!
Wh-What's up?
I'm not slacking off or anything.
I brought her order.
No, it's not about that.
Th-Then what's the problem?
If something happened,
we can talk outside...
Staaare
Stare...
Sweat
So, what kind of relationship do you two have?
Eek! She really does suspect something!
Whoa, where did that come from?
Nope! She can't know the truth!
This is one explosive situation!
What kind? Just normal classmates.
Right, Kazu-kun?
Y-Yeah, right.
C-Come on, Ruka-chan.
You're being rude to our customer.
Why do you ask, though?
Wait, I got it!
Do you like Kazu-kun, Ribbons?
You're such a playboy.
Well, no, it's more than that.
I'm his—
Kazu-kun? What was that?
Never mind!
Our boss banned her from chatting!
Why, Kazuya-kun?
Why are you hiding it?
Because we're at work?
But he's panicking too much for that.
And then there's what I heard earlier!
We went to karaoke together twice, didn't we?
Now I remember...
He said he turned to Chizuru-san
after being dumped by his ex.
His ex!
It's her! She's his ex!
If she is, then what is all this?
That attitude! Those eyes!
And asking if I like him!
And calling me "Ribbons"
In that case, what's her deal?!
She's acting like Kazuya-kun is still hers!
Wait, is he hiding it because she's his ex?
Is he still into her, then?
Even if he's not, she's still the
only girl he's actually dated!
So I'm...
in third place?!
Likes her
Just
dating her
Liked her
No! I can't accept that!
A-Anyway, let's talk outside.
Clack
We're dating!
I'm Kazuya-kun's girlfriend!
"Girlfriend"?
Karaoke Village
God, just kill me.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Wha?
"Girlfriend"? Really?
C-Calm down, Ruka-chan!
I-It's not like that, Mami-chan.
I can explain.
Yes, really!
You're his ex, aren't you?
Too bad for you! I'm his girlfriend now!
Which means Kazuya-kun belongs to me now!
Hey, Ruka-chan! What are you even saying?!
Also, I think you have the
wrong idea about something!
Acting all cool because you're his ex...
What, you think you're special to him
because you were his first? Are you serious?!
Sure, he leers at every cute girl
he sees, so he may seem easy!
Hey, that's not...
Not
wrong...
But he's not hung up on you
anymore! Not in the least!
Seriously, what's your deal?!
You show up at your ex's workplace?
You're the one who can't let him go, huh?
Stop, Ruka-chan! You can't say that!
Sucks to be you!
Kazuya-kun's totally smitten with me now.
An ex or two
is no big deal.
We've gone all the way, too!
What?! No, we haven't!
We have not!
I even spent an oh-so-passionate
night at his place recently.
He kept going, "Ruka, I love you!
I love you so much,"
and just wouldn't stop!
No, I didn't!
And you know it!
Anyway, you're a thing of the past!
Get out of his life already, will you?
Sorry. I didn't mean to...
You have a real girlfriend, huh, Kazu-kun?
But then...
Why do you still need a rental girlfriend?
Oh, well, you know...
It shows how accepting I am.
I know I'm his number one.
So I send him off...
Not
convincing.
M-Mami-chan, like I said,
it's just social research.
I see.
Sorry.
I should leave.
I'll leave the money here.
Huh? Wait...
Welp. She's gonna hate me forever.
Come on, Ruka-chan!
What was with that out... burst?
Waaah
But I am your girlfriend!
Oops.
Uwaaaaaah
Drag Drag
You'll bother our customers!
What's her problem? I hate her!
I love you!
I'm the one who loves you more than anyone!
Augh, just kill me now!
Yo, you by yourself?
Let me carry your stuff.
Buzz off.
S-Sorry.
Holy...
What was with that kid?
She's out of her mind.
I hear from Kibe-chan that
he's working and go to see,
and he has a girlfriend? Excuse me?
So that bag in his apartment was hers?
But is she really his girlfriend?
Something seemed off about him.
Would he really go out with that nutcase?
She knew about the rental girlfriend thing,
and she accepted it?
That makes no sense.
Besides, that design was more
"adult woman" than "teen."
Oh, yeah, this is his stop...
You're the one who can't let him go, huh?
Why the heck am I wasting time
thinking about all this?
Huh?
M... Mami-san?
What?
Who knows about Chizuru-san?
Well, there's us... and Kazuya's family?
His family?
His family knows her, too? Yikes.
That reminds me, he did ask me
to meet his grandma, didn't he?
So, he introduced her and couldn't
worm out of it for a year?
Then it could still be going on.
Oh, people at his workplace might know, too.
Huh? Workplace?
Kazu-kun got a job?
Yeah, at the KaraVillage by the next
station over, at the start of the year.
The Karaoke Village by
the next station over?
Mizuhara Chizuru
A pure and refined
high-class girlfriend
Sweat
Er... It's been a while.
Have a seat.
I had something to take care of around here.
And you? Do you live here?
Oh, no, I was here to do something, too.
Where are you headed?
Ikebukuro.
Really? Me, too!
Let's enjoy the ride.
That's a really nice bag.
It's from CoCo's latest
collection, right? Is it new?
No, I've had it for a while.
Cool. You've gotta buy the
fashionable stuff immediately,
before new stuff comes out
and it goes out of style.
When did you get it? Early April? Late?
Early, I think?
I see!
Sorry!
I just found it kinda funny.
I'm switching lines over this way.
How about you?
To the station exit.
Oh.
Guess this is it. See you... Actually,
we don't know if we'll meet again, huh?
I suppose not.
Bye.
Let me just ask you one thing.
You're not seeing Kazu-kun anymore, right?
That's right.
Okay, got it.
Bye.
Was that a coincidence? It was, right?
That settles it.
There's no doubt about it.
That bag was Mizuhara Chizuru's.
The timing fits. Did she forget it with him?
But who forgets their bag?
Was she there back then?
Either way, they're way closer
than rental GF and client.
What's with that kid, then?
She knows about her.
Is he two-timing? What the heck?
Maybe I'll find out more
if I check his follows.
Kinoshita Kazuya
@jrvbwr34bhcmdl-082 is blocked.
Are you sure you want to view these tweets?
Learn more
Unblock
Cancel
Ruka
For moots only. I love everything that's fun
Shit, she's locked.
Nagomi Sake Shop
I'm the shop's second owner, Kinoshita Nagomi!
Loving 77-year-old. I tweet about nihonshu
and I'm smitten with my grandson's girlfriend!
His family, huh?
Follow
Following
We somehow made it through that mess, but...
Those two are so tiring.
Tiring? You meanie!
How rude.
That's not what she meant.
What did she mean, then?
You have a duty to explain, Kazuya-kun.
Uh, Mizuhara was...
Now, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
She ran away!
"Youth and...
...Girlfriend."
If you can't explain, I might show up
in the next episode's preview, too!
"Youth and Girlfriend"
Look forward to it.